Baywatch: Hawaiian Wedding is a action, drama,
adventure film directed by Douglas Schwartz.
Mitch Buchannon, believed to have died in a boating accident survived and only
has amnesia, he has been recovering in a Los Angeles hospital.
His new fiancée, Allison Ford, resembles his old lover, Lt.
Stephanie Holden who died years ago.
Mitch Buchannon, played by David Hasselhoff.
C. J. Parker, played by Pamela Anderson.
Allison, played by Alexandra Paul.
Caroline Holden, played by Yasmine Bleeth.
Jack 'J.D.' Darius, played by Michael Bergin.
Taylor Walsh, played by Angelica Bridges.
Baywatch: Hawaiian Wedding is a 2003 American made-for-television
action comedy film directed by Douglas Schwartz.
The film reunited the original cast members of the television series Baywatch.
The story revolves around an old nemesis who threatens Mitch's
wedding day as his friends and fellow lifeguards reunite.
The film premiered on February 28, 2003 on Fox.
Filming for the film began in September 2002 on Turtle Bay Resort, Oahu, Hawaii.
The tone is emotional.